Magical Girl
Shiorin
Magical Girl Shiorin!
Episode 27
A New Ally
"A New Ally"!
I'm so, so sorry...
I suppose this might be a job for me,
as the previous Demon Lord...
No, it's all right.
I want to introduce you to
a new member of our team, A. Kina-san.
Hey there!
He's fully prepared,
so feel free to rely on him.
Then if I had another broken compact...
You broke it again?!
Let's make it quick.
There you go.
Wow!
Why would someone so talented work with us...?
Apparently, he went as far
with his old job as he could,
and now wants to contribute more to society.
What the heck?! Was he a CEO?
*
He
used
to be
the
Demon
Lord
Hey, hey, you around, Demon Lord?
Mentor!
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm working with the magical girl now.
Seriously, what are you doing?!
I've actually got some
handy information about her.
Handy information?!
I get it! My mentor is working as a spy
to discover the enemy's weaknesses...
Magical Girl Shiorin...
What about her?
She really values loyalty in a man.
How is that handy information?!
Should I not have told you?
It's good to know! Thank you very much!
To be continued!
To be continued! Maybe!
Maybe!
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#10 Even If We're Just Playing, He's My Kohai...
This year is the 40th anniversary
of our company's founding.
Sunpick Ltd.
40th Anniversary
Event
It was through your contributions
that we made it this far.
40th Anniversary
Thank you!
And once again, we're holding a competition
between new hires this year!
New Hire Contest
A new hire competition?
It's a intracompany competition
for employees in their first year.
When the manager was in his first year,
his proposal won him the MVP award for that year.
It went on to actually
be produced, became a huge hit...
Earning him the MVP award for that year.
Isn't that amazing?
I feel bad for the other rookies
who were hired at the same time.
That said...
You're actually kind of amazing, huh, Manager?
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
Nah, I am!
Here we have our theme for this year!
Subject:
Meowtaro
A new way of promoting him!
And for the department that
our most promising hire works in—
An opulent trip to a luxury resort
in sunny southern Okinawa!
Supreme Opulence!
Luxury Resort
Okinawa... A luxury resort...
I bought a new swimsuit for the occasion.
What do you think, Shinozaki-san?
I...
I'm gonna work hard!
So motivated!
But I'll have to handle
my regular duties, too...
I'll manage your task balance!
I'll help, too, of course!
So will Hayakawa-san.
I guess I don't mind pitching in...
Work hard to win that most promising
hire award, Shinozaki-san!
Senpai...
I'll do just that! Let's all go
to that tropical resort together!
Yeah!
So that's why you're so fired up.
I wanna live up to their expectations!
That said, I still don't have a concrete
idea for my proposal yet...
What about you, Yamagishi-kun?
Not interested. Too big a pain.
Supreme Opulence!
Luxury Resort
What about the luxury resort?
Even less interested.
Think about who's in PR, dude...
Could you pwease help wif dis?
Don't wanna.
Yuri-tan.
Masa-tan.
Bluh...
I doubt I'd enjoy it at all.
I guess I'm sorry?
You really hit the jackpot,
though, Zakishino...
You got a 5-star senpai with a 5-star boss to boot!
Could you not treat the people in my
department like gacha characters?
Employment
Agent
Maybe I oughta contact a job agent and
see about trying a reset marathon...
I'm telling you, it tasted amazing.
Speak of the devil...
There's 5-star senpai.
And there's no limit!
There's not?!
Plus, the interior is so cute.
We're both rookies and we make
the same money, but look at the difference!
Is life just pure RNG?!
With a senpai like that I'd be
willing to work Monday to Friday
for nine hours a day,
minus one hour for lunch, too!
You should be able to do that anyway.
Be real with me. How are
things going, Zakishino?
With what?
Don't play dumb.
With you and Katase-paisen!
I mean, she came to check on you
at your house...
And you went on a trip
together, right? Right? Right?
Nothing... happened...
Unbelievable. What, you see
those boobs and just feel nothing?
Don't talk so bluntly about boobs!
I-I mean...
I guess I can't say it's been
absolutely nothing.
Holy crap, the deed's already done?!
Give him back! I want
my pure-hearted Zakishino back!
I'm still pure, actually!
Five minutes left of lunch.
Uh... you're Kurusu-san, right?
Development Group 1
Kurusu Akari
That's Kurusu Akari from Development Group 1!
Watch yourself, Zakishino!
She was hand-picked
as the rising star of Group 1
by their charismatic, high-minded chief!
She's got the hottest rep out of anyone
who joined up the same year as us...
And she's favored to win
the most promising rookie contest!
Time should be productive, not wasted...
If you want to progress to the next stage.
That does sound high-minded!
You were also discussing... breasts.
That's sexual harassment.
You're right, it is.
Not when it comes to Zakishino
and Senpai. They're mutually in love.
Yamagishi-kun?!
The partner is... his senpai?
She's abusing her authority, then?
Wha?!
Exploiting her power.
Senpai isn't—
Chill out, Zakishino. Leave this to me.
This ain't no abuse.
Because the two of them are going out!
Also not true!
Workplace romance... Can't understand.
We don't provide matchmaking services here.
Yet, according to surveys, more than a quarter
of married couples met at work.
It's totally natural.
Easy, now...
Kurusu.
This is rare. You normally
don't stick around in the break room.
Development Group 1 Chief
Takatsukasa Shinobu
Director Takatsukasa...
Waste of time... won't be able
to get back to work right away...
Don't worry about it.
You've still got four minutes.
The crucial thing is being able to
switch your state of mind around.
Mistakes and regrets will be fuel
to carry you to the next stage.
Right!
She really is high-minded,
and charismatic, that chief...
S-So bright!
You're Shinozaki-kun from Dev Group 2, yes?
Yes.
Your manager and I joined
the company at the same time.
I make it a point to keep up
with Group 2's new hires.
You and Manager? That'd mean...
Isn't that amazing?
I feel bad for the other rookies.
She's who I felt bad for!
Something wrong?
No, nothing!
Akina and I have been friendly rivals
who've spurred each other on to
greater heights, even back then.
That said, he's always proven
to be more talented...
His proposal blew mine away.
Celebrating Product
Development Group 2's Major Hit
And the product that came from it was a hit—
I've had my hands full
just trying to catch up to him.
But before I realized it, I had been promoted
faster than anyone in company history.
And he's stopped
making as many obvious waves...
But I still can't forget it.
Those days when competing with him
raised both of our games higher and higher...
And I've realized something.
I need him!
I've already spoken to the president about it.
I see.
Well, if Kurusu-kun can win
the most promising rookie competition,
I'll consider transferring Akina-kun.
If I lose the contest...
the manager's going to get transferred?!
Development Group 2
Development Group 1
Oh, no!
Since when did he become the heroine?
Cut that out! That's just gonna
confuse me more!
I thought it'd be unfair if you didn't know.
Granted, we're bound to win...
so don't feel too torn up about it.
It's time, Kurusu.
Right.
Wait a second!
You might need him,
but I don't intend on handing our manager over.
I'm going to win that
most promising rookie award.
That's a good look in your eye.
One that's looking towards the next stage.
That said...
The competition... I won't lose to anyone.
I'll win most promising rookie.
We're taking this.
And Kurusu will go on to aim
for even greater heights.
Well, that got real competitive
all of a sudden!
Yeah.
Fantastic!
That was fantastic, Shinozaki-kun!
A heated battle between subordinates,
on behalf of their bosses!
So nice!
You should fight, too, Yamagishi-kun! For me!
Ishiyama-san, no one wants you, so I can't.
Wow, what a turn of events
for the rookie contest!
Are you even listening?
A battle over me!
No, seriously...
Good luck out there, Yamagishi-kun!
There's no fight here.
The new hire contest...
Good luck!
I don't need encouragement.
You do!
No!
I can't lose, no matter what!
Good luck!
No lo necesito.
Product Development
Group 2
Manager, about my project
for the competition...
Look at that!
That tea stalk is standing up!
I bet that's a good sign for something!
I hope so. Having green tea
every once in a while is nice, too.
Sure is!
So carefree...
My Tiny Senpai.
I hope you'll play with me a whole lot!
Okay!
Aozora Preschool
So many toys!
I know this!
They're cute.
Be sure to thank the nice people for the toys!
Thank you!
Would you like to accompany me to the ball?
Me, too!
Then let's all dance together.
Onee-chan, draw Kyapicure!
Nice art!
Sure.
I want Meowjiro!
Okay, sure! I'll do my best!
The kids seem really thrilled.
Yeah!
I didn't know we oversaw
product tests like this.
We see how they play with them,
and make adjustments based on that.
We don't get many chances for this,
so get as much research done as you can.
It might help with your contest.
Right!
The contest, huh...
Did you tell Senpai?
I don't want her to worry, though...
So I haven't told her about Manager yet.
I have to say...
Hey, come over here!
What should we play?
Okay!
She's so motherly!
The kids are drawn to her effortlessly...
Downright Madonna-like!
But more than that...
Welcome home, honey.
Wife factor...
High!
Do your job.
I-I know!
Okay, what do you guys wanna play?
Um, let me think..
With this? Or maybe this?
He broke the ice so easily.
That's Shinozaki-san.
He's such a capable kohai.
And then there's...
how paternal he is!
All the kids he's
interacting with are smiling...
It's like he's some kind of all-father!
And more than that...
Welcome home, honey.
Husband factor...
High!
Stare...
Uh, well...
Wh-What should we do to play?!
Come on, Tomo-kun! Don't pull!
You're gonna rip Meowtaro!
Then, you let go, Marin!
What's wrong?
Let's play nice together.
I've got another Meowtaro right here.
I don't wanna play with some dumb doll.
But she's always playing
with them all by herself!
You noticed that, huh?
Do you want to play with her?
Wha...
Who'd wanna play with Marin?!
Did that hurt, Meowtaro?
There, there...
It's okay now. He's not hurt.
Do you usually play alone?
Yeah. My friends are the dolls.
I see. But I'd like you to play
with us, too, Marin-chan.
Then, let's play house!
House?
Onii-chan, you're the daddy.
Shinozaki-san's the daddy...
And you, Onee-chan...
Th-The way this is going...
Onee-chan, you're mommy!
Mommy?
Yeah! He's daddy and you're mommy!
Even if we're just playing... he's my kohai...
No! Mommy doesn't call daddy her kohai!
Th-Then...
Takuma-san.
Shiori-san.
Yay! Daddy! Mommy!
It's like a vision of the future!
No! The child is supposed to be
the star when you play house!
Onee-chan...
You'll be kitty!
And I'll be mommy. And you're kitty!
I'm... a kitty?
I guess Senpai seems like a cat to kids, too.
A cat... I mean, that is
a member of the family, but...
So I'm an animal, not a human...
Daddy, dinner is ready!
There, there.
Do you want to eat, too, kitty?
In that case...
Sit on Daddy's lap.
S-S-Sit... on Daddy's lap?!
No!
You have to sit for real!
If you don't wanna do that, then lie on it.
Like lie down?! In his lap?!
That'd be sexual harassment
and abuse of authority!
Serious charges!
But the child is the star
when you play house...
I should...
S-Senpai?!
There you go. Good girl.
Give the kitty pats, Daddy.
Patting her while lying around?!
Those are couple activities! In broad
daylight, in front of small children?!
But Senpai's a cat right now...
But I'm a cat right now...
G-Good girl...
Maybe life as a cat... wouldn't be so bad.
Okay, your food is here, kitty.
Eating off the floor...
but I'm a cat... I'm a cat.
Senpai is crawling around on the ground...
Yum-meow!
We're done eating,
so let's have a picnic in the sandbox!
But there's a shark inside, so be careful.
A shark at a picnic?
Be careful now, Mommy.
I'm Mommy!
R-Right! Sorry!
Oh, Shinozaki-san...
The castle I made with Daddy and Kitty...
He's not a daddy, and she's not a cat!
And there's no sharks, either!
Sharks...?
Were you watching the whole time?
H-Hell no!
Why would I look at Marin?
Tomo-kun!
Shinozaki-san!
If you like a girl, be nice to her.
Sorry... you still mad?
I guess.
I really am sorry. Let's remake it...
And then can I play with you?
I guess that's fine.
So, when we play house, who will Tomo-kun be?
Tomo-kun is...
The shark.
The shark?!
He's mean, so he has to be
the shark that I hate.
Sh-Shark... the one she hates...
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
Come again!
Bye-bye!
See you next time!
Well, they were an energetic bunch!
They were...
I don't think I wanna draw
Kyapicure for a while.
You did draw a lot!
You're a star artist!
What did you think, Shinozaki-san?
Will today be useful for your proposal?
I think so.
It's kind of vague, but I'm starting
to get a vision for what I want.
I'll work hard so I can win
most promising rookie!
That's the spirit!
By the way, do you think those two will be okay?
You mean Marin-chan and Tomo-kun?
They had made up
by the time we were leaving.
I'm sure they'll be okay!
I think so, too.
If you like a girl, be nice to her.
Be nice to the girls you like...
Shinozaki-san is always nice to me, isn't he?
Is the cap stuck? I can open it for you.
Too hot? Let's turn the AC on.
So... so nice...
So nice!
Death By Nice
S-Senpai?!
Are you okay, Senpai?! What's wrong?!
I'm okay.
Adorable.
Use my handkerchief!
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar